<html>
	<title>ENGINE</title>

	<span>
		<p> Engine is the central I/O processing unit, redundantly built for high availablity. It consists of redundant directors ( director A and director B) that each contain multi-core CPUs, memory modules, and attach interfaces to universal I/O modules, such as front-end, back-end, InfiniBand, compression, and flash I/O modules.</p>
	</span>
	<span>
		<p> Engine cooling fans and power supplies can be accessed from the front, the I/O modules and the management module and control station can be accessed from the rear. Since the number of universal I/O modules used in the engine depends on the required functionality and the system storage capacity, some slots can remain unused.</p>
	</span>
	<span>
		<p> The engine rear view, I/O module slots, the physical and logical port numbering are depicted below.</p>
	</span>
	<span>
		<p>Physical port numbers</p>
	</span>
	<span><img src="phy_eng_ports_250f.gif" ratio="0.41"/></span>
	<span>
		<p>Logical port numbers</p>
	</span>
	<span><img src="logical_eng_phy_ports_250f.gif" ratio="0.398"/></span>
	<span>
		<p> The following table explains engine slot population rules:</p>
		<table>
			<tr>
				<td>Engine Slot Number</td>
				<td>Component</td>
				<td>Description</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>0</td>
				<td>Flash module</td>
				<td>Always populated, reserved for flash.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>1</td>
				<td>Flash module</td>
				<td>Optional, depends on the array’s storage capacity. Reserved for flash. </td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>2</td>
				<td>Universal front-end module</td>
				<td>Any Fibre Channel, or Ethernet I/O module can occupy this slot.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>3</td>
				<td>Universal front-end module</td>
				<td>Optional. Any Fibre Channel or Ethernet I/O module can occupy this slot.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>4</td>
				<td>Back-end I/O module</td>
				<td>Always populated, reserved for back-end.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>5</td>
				<td>Empty</td>

			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>6</td>
				<td>Flash module</td>
				<td>Optional, depends on the array's storage capacity, reserved for flash.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>7</td>
				<td>Compression module</td>
				<td>Always occupied</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>8</td>
				<td>Universal front-end module</td>
				<td>Optional. Any Fibre Channel,  or Ethernet I/0 module can occupy this slot.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>9</td>
				<td>Universal front-end module</td>
				<td>Optional. Any Fibre Channel,  Ethernet, or Compression I/0 module can occupy this slot.</td>
			</tr>
			<tr>
				<td>10</td>
				<td>InfiniBand I/O module</td>
				<td>Occupied in a multi-engine system.</td>
			</tr>
		</table>
	</span>
</html>
